Eteku Moses

Software Developer









Am a software engineer with skills in Android and iOS development using flutter framework. I have experience in web development and using web frameworks like WordPress and Laravel. Am also a graphics designer with more than 3 years of experience in graphics design.

WORK EXPERIENCES

Mobile App Developer

Makerere RIF | 2022 - Present

To develop a mobile application for E-community Governance of Catchment Restoration.

Mobile App Developer

Uganda Museum | 2021 - Present

To develop a mobile application that aids a digital visit of uganda museum majorly focusing on schools.

Mobile App Developer

St. Francis Chapel | 2021 - 2021

To develop a mobile application for livestreaming, recorded sermons, daily devotionals, church events.

Mobile App Developer

Landmark Millers | 2020 - Present

To develop a smartphone application that will be used to profile farmers and offer market to the products uploaded on the platform with digital payment integration.

Project Lead

Shamos Technologies | 2020 - Present

Am currently managing all software at shamostechnologies and as a project lead

Graphics Designer

ShamosTechnologies | 2019 - Present

My role is to make graphics for shamostechnologies for example logos, flyers, posters, banners etc.

PROJECTS

UMuseum Closed Source

A mobile app to offer digital visit to uganda museum

FuelMyFaith Closed Source

A Mobile App for St.Francis Chapel Makerere University Available on playstore.

AgriBiz Closed Source

An app for farm management in landmark millers company

Catchyshop Closed Source

Online shopping app available in Uganda. The app is for buying and selling of products.

Boda app(Solot Guy) Closed Source

App for ordering rides around Soroti city

Mentrogo Closed Source

A mobile app for online interaction

MCF Voting system Open Source

online voting system developed for students at Makerere university Uganda.

Link: https://github.com/etekumoses/mcfvotingsystem

SKILLS

Technical

Dart(Flutter Framework)

PHP

MySQL

Firebase

Professional

Effective communication

Project Management

Strong problem solver

Good time management

EDUCATION

Bsc in Computer Engineering
Makerere University
2017 - 2022

LANGUAGES

English (Professional)

INTERESTS

Watching

Playing Games

Travelling





